This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Mucky D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is exciting!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
As Luffy struggles to escape Impel Down and rescue his brother Ace,
Magellan stands in his way once again.
Go ahead.
Let the Sea Kings eat you and save me the trouble of cleaning up the mess.
House Judgment once more!
How come?
Giant!
Hold on!
Help me!
I said stop!
I'm glad you made it!
You must forgive me for making such an outlandish request back there.
It's a school of whale sharks!
Jinbei must have called them!
Awesome!
Come, final miracle!
Break through the gate of justice!
Parry them over here, friends!
Now that is handy!
Ha! Ha!
Yee-haw!
Whoa!
clearly hee-haw!
Bye!
Ah!
You're free!
Take that stupid poison guy!
Oh!
You can't breathe on two!
No more impel-down torture and to think I had almost given up hope!
It's not time to celebrate yet.
We still have a struggle ahead.
We won!
Thanks, guys!
You wheel sharks are awesome!
I've never forgotten you!
We saved our lives!
I'd better start treatment on Inazuma.
See what they've got stashed in the sickbay.
Right!
I'm never going back to that hellhole as long as I live!
Yeah, man, no more crime.
I'm heading home to be a family man.
Suck it, diarrhea man!
We're finally free!
That's right, you're free!
And thanks to who?
Say it loud!
Captain Buggy!
Yeah!
Hmm, resilient little insects.
Come in.
This is Warden Magellan.
Bring me a ship.
I can still chase them down.
Yes, sir!
Little do they know.
For all their joy, they've merely leapt from one cage straight into another.
You have been condemned and your sentence is final.
There is not but despair on the path before you.
However, you may struggle.
Rear Admiral, sir!
We have repaired the battery that was damaged by Jibay in the last battle.
Good work.
All ships, let's open fire!
We ha-ha-ha-ha!
A-Lot!
He-NO!
My pardon!
Correct Rage and fire again!
They're gonna sink us!
This is no way to die!
Come on, you guys, just let us go!
They've got a whole fleet!
We're dead!
We've done well enough so far,
since all of their high-ranking officers
have been summoned to Marine Corps,
but we're still outnumbered,
and they won't let us go so easily.
Can't you see how I see your time?
More filthy criminals such as you?
The gates of justice will never open!
Oh, crap!
I forgot about that thing!
We're going to crash right into it!
He can't!
Yeah!
Go dance or whatever that guy said!
Hey, come on now!
What are we going to do now, Shark?
Keep sailing!
You have lost your damn mind!
You trying to get us killed?
Why the hell are you so calm?
We're all about to die!
What'd you say, SharkBank?
Protect the ship!
The gate can come next!
Yeah!
Whoa!
Oh!
Yeah!
Why are we putting up with this crap?
This is a Navy ship, too.
Fire back, you imbeciles!
I was just about to see that!
On the cannons, men!
Give them hell!
Roger that, Captain Boyd!
Take this!
Save us!
A gun balloon!
Look on that!
Fire!
Dammit! There are way too many of them!
There's crew!
They're closing in and we're about to hit the gate!
What are we supposed to do?!
The stinkin' morons!
Where do they think they're going?
They expect the gate to just open like magic?
Yeah, good luck with that.
Magellan would have to hit the switch for them himself.
Guess the poor fools missed the memo on that one.
And fire!
Don't stop to their zonk!
Huh?
The gates of justice!
They're opening!
But why?
This doesn't make sense!
Contact impaled down!
It's opening!
Why is this happening?
A trap!
I don't know what's going on and I don't care!
As long as we're not dead and I can save Ace!
It's open!
I never know what's going on and I don't care as long as we're not dead and I can save these!
Let's open! Let's open! Let's open!
They're escaping!
Warden Magellan, hurry, please!
Hm? No. Wait.
Huh? Huh?
Huh? The gate! Who authorized this?
You're sure you want to open the gates of justice at a time like this?
Warden Magellan, sir?
Of course I am. Do you have any reason to doubt me?
No. I suppose not.
As soon as the prisoner's ship makes its way through, I want you to close the gate. Understood?
If you say so, sir.
We haven't lost them yet! Take a ship! Fire!
Did Magellan order this? What's he thinking?
Has anyone contacted the ward? Something isn't right here!
Actually, sir, I agree. We saw the warden at the pier a moment ago. The thing is, he seemed as confused about it as we are and just took off running.
When I find out who's responsible for this, I'm gonna wring their neck.
Damn it, Control Room! What are you doing? Who told you to open the gate of justice?
Uh, wait, uh, warden?
Huh?
Uh-ho!
All this time, you knew!
And that's why you didn't stop!
Ah-ah-ah! You bastard!
That's me!
I got you!
You silly man! Didn't learn your lesson the first time, did ya?
He was a fake all along!
I, uh, just heard from the lookout warden. They couldn't sink the pirates and they're heading through the gates as we speak.
Even if they manage to pass through, their fate is sealed. If they think they can escape an entire fleet of Navy vessels, they're fools!
We'll finish those bastards yet!
Still, we need not take any chances. Press the button and close the gate!
Uh, yes sir!
Let's see...
No problem!
Don't you dare! You step away!
Ah! Of course!
No!
Push it!
No, don't!
No!
Push it!
Push the button!
Yes sir!
And now, Memoirs of a Desert Jingle!
Are you guys suckers or what?
Ugh!
You will pay!
I'm not gonna let you lay a single finger on Straw Boy!
Look! They're trying to close the gate hours!
That's good! As long as we can make it through in time that it'll slam in their faces and we'll be free to go!
Damn it! Von was with us just a second ago! Everyone else is leaving and he stayed back all by himself?!
I wouldn't even be here if it wasn't for his help! I'd probably be dead!
He helped us find Eva! And he helped us escape! He saved me from that poison and cheered for me the whole way!
He's my friend!
And he's my friend!
Look!
Look! They're trying to close the gate hours!
That's good! As long as we can make it through in time that it'll slam in their faces and we'll be free to go!
Damn it! Von was with us just a second ago!
Everyone else is leaving and he stayed back all by himself?!
I wouldn't even be here if it wasn't for his help! I'd probably be dead!
He's my friend and you wanna go without him?!
There's no time!
We can't just leave him to die back there!
You listen! This is the only way anyone could make it! We've left immeasurable comrades behind!
Do you want to go back and fight Magellan again? And risk losing even more friends?
What if we hadn't stayed behind to open the gate? Then where would we be right now? Dead or worse!
If anyone can get the gate open for you guys, it's me!
Don't worry your pretty little blue head!
I don't doubt that you can succeed, but then what?
Let's not ask silly questions, alright?
But do me a favor and don't tell Strawboy until communications are cut!
Swans never die and never say goodbye!
It's still connected.
Baby transponder snails have limited coverage. Once the gate closes, you won't be able to speak to it.
No good! It's a total mess! We can't fix this! Not in time to stop them at least!
You dare to mark the warden? You'll pay for this!
I knew memorizing your face was a good idea!
Wake up you imbecile! What the hell happened here?
Please! You're choking me!
And touch!
I curse you!
God! God!
Strawboy?
Hey! Can you still hear me? It's Loopy!
Are you nuts? Why are you doing this?
It's just like last time!
Great Bard Clay!
Running now would go against everything Bard Clay stands for!
If we abandon allies who are risking their lives to pick up a friend,
could we live with ourselves tomorrow?
Listen guys! Straw hats too!
What I must say is of great importance!
So tell me something! I am the straw hat you idiots are looking for, right?
Oh, Emma! Miss Hina! The sheep ship is heading east!
You must be feeling pretty stupid right now falling for such a simple trick!
See, we're masters of disguise!
As well as friends to the straw hats!
Bring it on, sister!
Why didn't you say something?
Maybe we could have found another way!
Ji-Fei, you promised you what Bard to tell him until later!
This is the last thing I wanted!
We were supposed to break out together, weren't we?
Damn it! How many times do you have to save me, huh?
If you're there, say something! Answer!
He saved us!
We're only free now, because he stayed behind in that hell!
Come on!
Brother, please! We just want to talk to you!
Let us know you're alive, okay? Say something!
Come on!
Mr. Two!
How dare you, Mr. Two!
Before I can tell you, I'm sorry!
Bond boy!
Fire!
Don't let them get through that gate!
Blow them to smotheries!
Run!
Mr. Two!
This is it! The gate's about to close!
We have... to go!
So thank you!
We'll never forget you!
Oh, my God!
Straw boy!
I'm here!
Find Ace! Save him!
And don't look back!
I know you can do it!
And you have lots of friends to help you!
Fine!
The gate is closing!
Keep firing!
Take them out!
Did you miss me, old pal?
Yeah, we did!
We really did it!
Oh, stop pulling my tail!
Straw boy, I'm here to rescue you!
Oh, my God!
I've got you down!
The gate is closing!
Keep firing!
Take them out!
Did you miss me, old pal?
Yeah, we did it!
We really did it!
Oh, stop pulling my tail!
Straw boy, I've come here to rescue you!
In the name of our ever-lasting friendship!
Hang in there!
You have to live!
Strawboy!
Swans never die and never say goodbye.
Resort!
I can't believe this.
Take out a way!
We owe him our lives. We're finally free!
If it wasn't for him, we'd be sitting at the bottom of the ocean right now.
Even in the depths of hell, the flower of friendship shall still bloom,
flames licking at its stem.
And on the sands of the river where souls part from the living,
it sheds a solitary petal, leaving it behind as a memento.
So let us vow that we shall make it bloom again someday.
Oh, come my way!
Brother Clive!
Any last words before I eliminate you?
Hang on me!
Let us meet again in the garden of Oh, Come My Way!
And suddenly, in one fell swoop, the number of prisoners that had escaped from Impel Downjump from one to 241.
And yet, this is only the beginning of a turn of events that will shake the entire world.
The public execution of Portgus D. Ace will take place in four hours.
After a tearful farewell to Bon Clay, Luffy and the others prepare for the next step of their plan to rescue Ace.
However, Buggy and the other escaped prisoners are against traveling to Navy Headquarters.
That is, until a sudden transponder snail call reveals a secret that no one could have imagined.
On the next One Piece, to the Navy Headquarters, off to rescue Ace.
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
King of the Pirates!
Thank you.